There was a really strange tweet from
Kirby that said something like four
words. Is there any kind of update on
his status?
>> I don't I don't know. I I don't know
about the tweet. No, I mean he's he'll
be running around doing some individual
stuff like that. Um you know, he's doing
a little bit more, but I I don't know
anything about the tweet.
>> Coming back this week against Cowboys.
>> I mean, he's closer than he was um
before. you know, he's he's close. Um,
you know, it'll we'll know a lot more
really tomorrow. You know, today's a
walk through, so tomorrow, Friday, see
where he's at. Um, but he is getting
better. Like we said, he gets better
every week.
>> Yes. Obviously didn't expect him to be
out this long, otherwise maybe he would
have gone on on IR. What What's is it
just a pain management thing? What What
has been like the the holdup? Exactly. A
lot of it is just trying to um get some
stability, you know, uh in the leg and
uh get some strength, get some
stability, which in turn will help some
of the pain, but but also some of the
wear and tear. You know, the stronger
you get it in there, it stabilizes it
and so it doesn't
um you know, wear out as fast or create
that kind of pain with it. So um that's
really what a lot of it is right now. Is
this something you you pretty confident
will clear up when he has the offseason
arrest or is there concern of crime?
>> Yeah, I don't know. I mean, I I that's
hard to say. Um I don't think it's
necessarily going away, but I think you
do the best you can to manage it. You
know, that's uh it's like a lot of these
guys um you know that have have gotten
some injuries here or deals with could
be cartilage or meniscus or anything
like that. It's you do your best to
manage it and you know they'll there'll
always be a little wear and tear and
it's just you know how bad is it you
know but I do know that the more you can
strengthen and stabilize uh it that
helps a ton helps with the swelling
helps with the pain. Um so it's where
we're at.
>> What is his exactly? Is it more than a
bone bruise then? Is he dealing with
something else? No, I mean I think it's
it's I think bone bruise was certainly
part of it, but it's also just, you
know, he's he's got some wear. He's got
a little wear, that's all.
>> Yesterday, um you were asked about the
pass rush and you said there, you know,
felt like there were three snaps where
you didn't get home that you thought you
should have. Um you know, that's still a
zero sack performance. So, if you're
getting the pressure you want, what what
do you need to do more as a overall
defense to to be getting home more and
not just getting the pressure?
>> Yeah. I mean, I I I think look, f first
of all, Love did a hell of a job. He's a
heck of a player, man. And uh you know,
that ball was coming out fast and he
threw you know, he threw a few of these
now off his back foot and uh and it was
on point. So, you know, he's got that
ability. But, um, you know, I I think
more than anything, it's, you know, you
do your best that you can to set up a
one-on-one where you can find one. Uh,
you're trying to fabricate some of
these. Most of them come up in third
down to where you you want to get your
guy in a one-on-one. Um, and then it's
up to him to win. And so it's, you know,
we had a few of those and we just we we
didn't uh, you know, we felt good about
the person that we had and we just
didn't quite get there in time. So, got
to be a little bit better. Um,
you know, and and fundamentally, it's a
little bit like what I told the defense,
we just, man, details and discipline and
really fundamentally, we got to get
better, you know, we we got to get
better. um you know and it can't just be
um you're going to win off talent, you
know, or
things of that nature, you know, it it
was really more about pointing out all
the things that have nothing to do with
talent. Um so which really is it it is
the details of discipline and the
fundamentals. So we just got to be a
little more on point there. We can
everybody's got to do their job and uh
and and that'll help. That'll go a long
way.
>> Whatever you up. Go ahead.
>> Coach, I was saying y'all been out in
Dallas the last couple years. Obviously
had the game out there. Y'all lost a
controversial one. Then y'all come back
last year. Y'all blown them. How is it
just to have Dallas at home this time
like and and host that team here?
>> Yeah. I mean, I feel like we've been out
there three times, three or four times.
I don't know. Has it been three or is it
two? I don't know what it is. Um, so
yeah, to be able to get them back home,
you know, that's that's that's good.
That's different, you know, cuz you um
but they're playing good football right
now. Uh you know, playing with a lot of
confidence, man. They've beefed up that
defense. Uh it's a really good Dline. Uh
those guys are active. Uh I flu has done
a hell of a job. You know, he's a good
defensive coordinator. We know him.
Obviously, he was in this division. Uh
defense always played well. Um but he's
doing a good job. And then, you know,
what shot he's done offensively over
there. and and Prescott. Uh those two
receivers, they got a run game. Old
Lions rugged. Um it's it's a it's a um
it's a good team. It's a it's a good
team, man. This this is a this is a real
good team playing at a high level,
confident football. So, this should be a
good test for us, man. We're we're
pretty fired up
>> the last three years. I was just going
to ask being how good they are since
Quinnon Williams came aboard, what sort
of impact he's had on on that defense
and kind of how they've played the last
few weeks with with him in the middle. I
mean, he helps, you know, I mean, he
helps those guys. Um, you guys know how
I feel about Kenny Clark. I think he's
he's an outstanding player. And so, you
know, that helps Kenny. Um, and and it
helps really the rest of them. Uh, 41
plays at a high level, man. He can burn
the edge. Um, you know, you got Clowny.
Um, they still got Fowler. I mean, they
So, they they got some guys now. 97's a
good player. You know, he can get an
edge. Uh but it really you you put you
know you put Quinnon in there man it you
know he's already a uh he's a good
player man you know run and pass gets
off the ball disruptive but then he he
really helps those guys around him he
does you know because now he there's
some resources you may need there and
and uh the rest of those guys they'll
get some five down stuff and let those
guys go. So it's a good unit but we just
faced a pretty good unit too.
>> Wanted to ask about Josh Pascal. He
didn't get activated last week. Did he
have a setback or just wasn't enough
time?
>> Yeah, it just it wasn't uh it just
wasn't enough time really uh to really
be able to say that we we knew he would
be able to get through the year or that
he was ready. That's that's what it came
down to. Um you know, hate it for him,
but it's it's it's where it was at.
>> How do you limit the uh explosives
against an offense like that?
Well, it's not easy. Um, it's not easy
cuz those look those two receivers, man.
Here's what they do a great job of and
it helps. So, you got you got two number
one receivers on the outside and both of
them are two different types of players.
So, that gives them variety,
versatility, but then they run the ball
well. They have a diverse run scheme.
Uh, they do a lot of under center Dak uh
they're against playing at a high level.
the run action, the play pass stuff has
been really good. So, when you can run
it like they run it and then you got
those guys and they got a pretty good
tight end, uh, man, they become
explosive. So, you know, I I'll go back
to this. So much of it is going to start
with shutting this run game down. We we
cannot let this run game get going. And,
uh, cuz those guys are a handful anyway
on the perimeter. Um, but if we can just
at least shut down some of this two
dimensional football, that's going to go
a long way for us. Just one more follow
up about Dallas. Like what what did you
take from the 2023 experience that's
become kind of legendary a little bit
here with the Dan Skipper game and what
that's become, but what did you take
from that experience particularly in the
end? Did you learn anything?
>> Uh,
no. I mean I I uh not really I mean that
was that was a crazy game, right? I
mean, that was, you know, everything
that that came down to and um had an
opportunity there at the end and just
didn't didn't wasn't able to close it
out. But there was a number of things.
Um I don't know if I'd say I learned
anything really. Um you know, I think
more than anything, it just uh makes you
mad. That's about it. Um
but but all good, man. You know, it was
if you're a fan, that was a heck of a
game. I know that. Um, you know, and you
try to, if anything, you get in that
situation again, you try to find a way
to win that one instead of, you know,
how do you keep it out of the hands of
the officials. That's really what you're
trying to do. Uh, just leave it, leave
it out of there, you know, that way it's
just up to you.
>> You ever seen a six lineman become a
cult hero like Skipper, too? It's crazy.
>> Not really. It's uh, you know, Skip's a
He's a different breed of man, so he's
something else. He does a good job, man.
He's I tell you what, he's dependable
now. He's reliable, dependable, and he
does a lot of jobs for us. So,
>> you um I want you said that 2023 game
makes makes you mad. It it does feel
like you put a little extra sauce into
the one last year. You guys opened up
the playbook and really took it to them,
gave them one of their worst losses in
franchise history at their place. Do you
think that there's carryover year to
year? Do you think maybe they're going
to be looking to to bring a little extra
into this one because of the way they,
you know, lost that game last year?
>> Uh, I don't know. I mean, I I uh I think
every every team's different. Every
year's different, but I know this they
want to win this game. I know that cuz I
know we want to win this game. So,
they're playing good football. They're
they're very much in that division race
over there right now and playoff race.
Uh we're an NFC opponent and I know that
they want to beat us. um you know so but
we want to win too and we need to win so
that's where this game's at.
>> Any any updates on Graham and and uh
Brock?
>> Yeah, Graham's doing he's better. Um
there again we walked through today and
then Brock, you know, really nothing
new. Nothing new from last week. You
know, we're still sending out scans for
for what he you know for this trachea.
Um, and just seeing if there's, you
know, any other second opinions that
that, uh, would change, I guess, his the
outlook for him playing, you know, and
right now there's there's really nothing
right now that would change that. So,
we're just kind of in a, you know, I
know that frustrates him. He wants to
play. Um, but we're just kind of in a
holding pattern right now.
>> That could be a longterm deal.
>> Yeah, it could be. Yeah, could be.
>> Yep.
What's that?
>> Follow up.
>> Yeah.
>> Does this feel I mean I know that you
don't ever consider a game a must-win
just given where you guys are and where
the division is going and what's at
stake against another important NFC
opponent battling for a playoff spot. Is
there part of that that may be a little
bit true at this juncture?
>> Well, we our margin for error is very
small right now. So, of course, we we
got to find a way to win and we want to
win, you know, and I think I go back to
this. I mean, we just lost one. We got
to find a way to win this next one in
front of us. And uh and yeah, I mean,
time's running out and uh so, you know,
um it's all about finding a way to win
the game. But, but I've also been in
these now before where we got counted
out uh when I was a player. You know, we
lost two in a row and we were almost ma
mathematically uh eliminated from the
playoffs. So that was all the writing
and then we we won out and uh got in,
you know. Um so you just man, you find a
way to win the one in front of you and
don't get caught up in the rest of the
stuff. That's the bottom line. We're in
this business to win. We're trying to
win. We got to win.
>> What year was that for you as a player?
I was up too.
>> Thank you.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hey, Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat. N. [music]
Oh,
[music] heat,
[music]
heat.